{
    "id": "ed4f009ef91c44a08fffe57b6df2a579",
    "title": "Combine the following sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ca06e3917c034ecf978e4fe9919c9819",
            "title": "Sentence Completion",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "......................... the thief, they handed him over to the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Caught",
                        "Having caught"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................ a noise, the thief ran away.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Hearing",
                        "Heard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ........................ to walk fast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too fat",
                        "so fat"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ........................ that she could not stand up.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too tired",
                        "so tired"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................... she left home at 4, she hasnâ€™t arrived yet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "As if",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................ the tortoise was slow, he beat the hare in the race.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................... you reach there before 3 pm, you will not be able to meet him. /",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................... hard you may work, you cannot please him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "However",
                        "Though",
                        "Even though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................... his illness, he attends office regularly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In spite of",
                        "Even though",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The apples ..................... I bought yesterday were good.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}